Hello everybody I'm Patricio
Lumbe I'm a AWS cloud and
DevOps engineer and today
I'd like to show you my project
That I built for a practical
problem imagine if your
Production breaks at 3:00 a.m in
the morning and nobody is
Watching so the alarm
triggers but the alarm cannot
Solve the problem
itself it still needs someone to
notice this problem
Solve this problem going through
logs and figuring figuring out
What happened and decide to fix
this
Problem in a traditional
process this can take hours even
Two or or three hours for a
business those three hours are
Not just an engineering
problem they can cause many
Other problems like a loss of
revenue
Or low productivity even a
potential poor customer
Experience that's why I decide
to build this project to address
this
Problem